TAUFIK HIDAYAT

Email: me@tfkhdyt.my.id | Portfolio: tfkhdyt.my.id | Phone Number: +62895338865375

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/tfkhdyt142 | GitHub: github.com/tfkhdyt

INTRODUCTION

I'm a Full Stack Developer and Computer Science Student from Bale Bandung University. I have experience as a Junior Web Developer. I have an interest in a career as a Full Stack Developer (TypeScript and Golang). I'm a fast learner and self-taught. I have learned a lot of new technologies in the past few years by myself from the Internet.

EDUCATION

Bale Bandung University

2020 - Present

Computer Science
Current GPA: 3.66

• "Best Academic Achievement" in MSIB Batch 5 at seKODlah (Forest Interactive)

• "Best Capstone Project Winner (Yukitanya)" in MSIB Batch 5 at seKODlah (Forest Interactive)

SMKN 7 Baleendah 2017 - 2020

Software Engineering

WORK EXPERIENCE

Netovas Eterna Teknologi

Dec 2023 - Present

Full Stack Developer

- Designing and implementing responsive and visually appealing user interfaces for a CRM application.
- Utilizing cutting-edge front-end technologies such as TypeScript, Next.js, and Tailwind CSS to create a seamless user experience.
- Design and implement RESTful APIs for seamless communication between the frontend and backend.
- Implement authentication and authorization mechanisms to ensure data security and user access control.
- Implement and maintain CI/CD pipelines to automate the testing, building, and deployment processes.
- Orchestrate deployment workflows using Docker/Podman, ensuring consistency across various environments.

Inovindo Digital Media

Jan 2019 - Mar 2019

Junior Web Developer Intern

- Develop an e-commerce website for resellers.
- Deploy websites that have been finished by the dev team to web hosting services.
- · Manage a company product list database.
- Publish articles for client's company blog.
- Improve client's website Search Engine Optimization.

SKILLS

Programming Language: Javascript, TypeScript, Golang.

Technologies: HTML, CSS, Git, React, Next.js, SvelteKit, Node.js, Express, Fastify, NestJS, AdonisJS,

Gin, Fiber, Tailwind CSS, UnoCSS.

DBMS: PostgreSQL, MySQL, SQLite, Redis.

Operating System: GNU/Linux, EndeavourOS, Arch Linux, Debian.

FEATURED PROJECTS

- Yukitanya A platform that connects many students into a discussion forum to complete schoolwork together.
- Pondokeun Lightweight, Modern, Free and Open Source Link Shortener.
- Shopping Store Multi-user e-Commerce REST API.
- KBBI Bot Telegram Bot to find word definitions from KBBI with web scraping method.
- <u>Auto-EPP</u> Program that automatically manages the energy performance preferences (EPP) of your
 AMD CPU using the AMD-Pstate driver.

See my other projects here »

CERTIFICATIONS

Best Academic Achievement (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 5)

seKODlah (Forest Interactive)

Credentials: Certificate

December 30, 2023

Best Capstone Project Winner (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 5)

seKODlah (Forest Interactive)

Credentials: Certificate

December 29, 2023

Mastering JavaScript (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 5)

seKODlah (Forest Interactive)

Credentials: Certificate

December 28, 2023

Scalable Web Service with Golang (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 4)

Hacktiv8 Indonesia

Credentials:

Certificate

• Transcript

June 30, 2023

Advanced Golang (Studi Independen Kampus

Merdeka Batch 4)
Hacktiv8 Indonesia

Credentials ID: 7e3a9212-f68e-4049-

ae4a-58ee5e4727c1

April 21, 2023

REST API With Golang (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 4)

Rampus Werueka Batch 4

Hacktiv8 Indonesia

Credentials ID: de104ded-519d-40ad-bccd-

<u>a2e23ca646b2</u>

March 20, 2023

Knowing How To Use A Database (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 4)

Hacktiv8 Indonesia

Credentials ID: b026050b-f76d-4e6d-

a89d-37fb32df14b3

March 14, 2023

Beginner Level Golang (Studi Independen Kampus Merdeka Batch 4)

Hacktiv8 Indonesia

Credentials ID: 58599276-c80b-40cc-8b9c-

fa3e4df68f2e

Mar 7, 2023

Become An Expert Back-End Developer (IDCamp 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: JLX1LV8L2X72

Feb 6, 2023

Junior Web Developer Competency Certificate

LSP Informatika

Credentials ID: 62019197272022

Oct 28, 2022

Building a Cloud Architecture on AWS (IDCamp 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 4EXG9YK61ZRL

Oct 18, 2022

Learn Computer Networking for Beginners (DevOps and Back-End Developer Scholarship Program)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 0LZ0GDQQKX65

Oct 17, 2022

Learn DevOps Basics (DevOps and Back-End Developer Scholarship Program)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: <u>JLX1L0R92X72</u>

Oct 14, 2022

Learn the Fundamentals of Back-End Applications (IDCamp 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: RVZKK9K7NZD5

Oct 12, 2022

Learn to Create Front-End Web for Beginners (Lintasarta Cloudeka Digischool 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 0LZ01WRYKP65

Oct 7, 2022

Learn Basic Web Programming (Lintasarta Cloudeka Digischool 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: 07Z6RNWQYPQR

Sep 16, 2022

Junior Web Developer Training (Vocational School Graduate Academy

Digital Talent Scholarship

Credentials ID:

VSGA/2022/3460/1503460101-394

Sep 7, 2022

Cloud Practitioner Essentials: Learn AWS Cloud Basics (IDCamp 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: KEXLGL69RZG2

Jun 19, 2022

Learn JavaScript Programming Basics (IDCamp 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: <u>4EXG55KNGXRL</u>

May 29, 2022

Learn to Create Back-End Applications for Beginners (IDCamp 2022)

Dicoding Indonesia

Credentials ID: <u>4EXG55M9EXRL</u>

Jun 1, 2022